[
    {
        "question": "1. Can you explain the term RPA?",
        "answer": "RPA stands for Robotic Process Automation. It is a business process automation technology that uses software robots or bots to automate business processes.\nA workflow with several steps and applications can be taught to the software or robot, such as receiving forms, sending a receipt message, checking the form for completeness, filing the form in a folder, and updating a spreadsheet with the name of the form, the date submitted, and so on.\nRPA software is designed to relieve employees of a load of repeated and monotonous activities.\nBe UiPath Certification ready. Enroll in RPA Course in New York offered by Intellipaat.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "automation-anywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "2. What is Automation Anywhere?",
        "answer": "Automation Anywhere is one of the prominent RPA tools that offers a variety of sophisticated features for automating complex business processes. It’s a web-based management solution for automating repetitive, rule-based operations that are now done by humans.\nIt provides enterprises with an end-to-end automation plan. Automation Anywhere’s main goal is to provide scalable, secure, and robust services to its users.\nPreparing for a Job Interview! Check out our blog Selenium Interview Questions now.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "automation-anywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "3. Why do we require Automation Anywhere?",
        "answer": "For a variety of reasons, Automation Anywhere must be employed. They are as follows:\nIt saves both time and money.\nThere is no need for programming skills; we can record our own actions.\nSpeeds up transaction times.\nRemoves the possibility of human error.\nScaling up from the desktop to the data center\nIt’s non-intrusive and has a short time to value.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "automation-anywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "4. Can you explain what are the advantages of Automation Anywhere?",
        "answer": "The advantages of Automation Anywhere are as follows:\nThere is no complex programming required, and it also supports the front-end.\nAutomation Anywhere is a user-friendly UI with drag-and-drop functionality.\nIt has a platform-independent policy and is simple to integrate with other systems.\nIt’s used across the board since it allows many departments to focus on tasks that require human engagement.\nNavigates across diverse digital environments.\nIt is intended for complexity and can perform difficult jobs rapidly.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "automation-anywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "5. What are the features of Automation Anywhere?",
        "answer": "The following are the main features of Automation Anywhere:\nIt allows for script-free automation. So no programming knowledge is required.\nProvides sophisticated business solutions for IT and business needs from automation intelligence.\nSMART Automation Technology is used to distribute functions across multiple systems.\nIt is simple to automate complex and time-consuming activities quickly.\nCreate various tasks for automation, such as logging keystrokes and mouse clicks.\nDistribute tasks over a number of computers.\nScriptless Automation is available from Automation Anywhere.\nEven when the computer is locked, auto-login keeps running scheduled tasks.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "automation-anywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "6. What are the three types of Automation Anywhere bots?",
        "answer": "The three types of Automation Anywhere tools are:\nMeta bots: Meta bots are the building blocks of automation. It’s built-in such a way that you only have to make minor adjustments to the bot when the app is updated or changed. Any process that uses that bot is automatically updated.\nIQ bots: It is a sophisticated instrument. It has the ability to learn on its own and complete tasks in accordance with its instructions. Automation is provided by IQ Bot, which employs cutting-edge cognitive technologies. It is based on the idea of organizing unstructured data while also enhancing its abilities and performance.\nTask bots: In domains like document administration, HR, claims management, IT services, and more, task bots automate a rule-based, repetitive process. This results in an instant increase in productivity, reduced errors, and cost savings.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "automation-anywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "7. Do you know about Predefined variables?",
        "answer": "Predefined variables are system variables that Automation Anywhere makes available in order to automate any task. Go to the Variable Manager on the right-hand side of the task pane and select Show System Variables to see the predefined variables. This will allow you to access the system variables.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "automation-anywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "8. What is QTP?",
        "answer": "QuickTest Professional is the full form of QTP. QTP is an automated functional testing tool that assists testers in running automated tests to find any flaws, faults, or gaps in the application under the test’s expected outcomes. Mercury Interactive created it, which was eventually acquired by HP and is now MicroFocus.\nWatch this tutorial video on Automation Anywhere",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "automation-anywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "9. Can you give some applications where Automation Anywhere can be used?",
        "answer": "The following are some of the most common applications for Automation Anywhere. They are as follows:\nIn the financial/accounting department, for invoice processing, reporting, and auditing, among other things.\nIn the HR department, Using PeopleSoft to automate tasks.\nIn the marketing department, Creating lead generating reports and monitoring social sentiment are two aspects of marketing.\nIn Sales, Creating and printing invoices, as well as entering, modifying, and deleting customer information in CRM.\nFor ERP (Enterprise Resource Planning) integration in the manufacturing department.\nIn the government sector, for filling out subcontractor forms and automating daily reporting.\nIn the retail industry, to collect product information from a manufacturer’s website.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "automation-anywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "10. What are various Automation Anywhere tools?",
        "answer": "There are various automation tools for testing. QTP, Robotium, SoapUI, and Telerik Test Studio are some of the most important for automated anywhere testing.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "automation-anywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "11. How many automation commands are available in Automation Anywhere?",
        "answer": "In the AAE Client Task Editor, there are roughly 575 commands in Automation Anywhere’s command library such as KeyStroke, Message Box, LogFile, Object Cloning, Excel Command, Email Commands, DB Commands, Clip Board, and many more.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "automation-anywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "12. Can you differentiate between the wait command and the delay command?",
        "answer": "The main difference between the Wait and Delay commands is the argument you specify when using them. When you wish to wait for the components on the screen or the screen itself to change, you can use the Wait command.\nThe Delay command, on the other hand, is used to improve the performance of activities in a task while working on loops.\nWait command is good compared to delay. Because you have two reasons: Wait for the window to open and the screen to change.\nThe delay command allows you to specify whether you want to delay for a particular amount of time or for a randomized amount of time depending on a provided range.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "automation-anywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "13. Do you know how many recorders are there in Automation Anywhere and what are they?",
        "answer": "Screen recorder: The Screen Recorder is the most practical method for efficiently automating the operation. It can be used to record user actions such as mouse clicks and movements, keystrokes, and so on.\nSmart Recorder: In desktop programs, the Smart Recorder is used to record objects such as drop-down menus, checkboxes, list boxes, radio buttons, and more. ‘Object recorder’ is another name for it.\nWeb recorder: The Web Recorder is mostly used to gather information from the internet. It can accurately capture user activities on web-based tasks and then automate them without the need for coding knowledge.\nTask editor: The task editor is used to combine many instructions to process any command. This editor allows you to open and edit numerous tasks at the same time. Commands panel, Task Actions List, Action Buttons, Error View and Variable Manager Panel, and Filters are all part of the task editor.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "automation-anywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "14. What are the components of Automation Anywhere tool architecture?",
        "answer": "A distributed architecture is used in Automation Anywhere. Bot Creators and Bot Runners are the two main components of the architecture. Both of these elements are linked to the Control Room. The control room will be the centralized manager in this architecture.\nLearn more about Automation Anywhere with Automation Anywhere Tutorial.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "automation-anywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "15. Can you mention tasks that can be automated?",
        "answer": "The tasks which can be automated are data entry, repetitive tasks, a Smoke-testing suite, Build deployment, Behind Graphical User Interface(GUI) automation, scanning documents, data preparation, and many more.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "automation-anywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "16. What is Sikuli?",
        "answer": "Sikuli is a tool that can be used to automate web components, or the graphical user interface(GUI). All site elements are saved in the project in Sikuli. This utility takes into account things like photos and uses VIM to trigger Graphical User Interface interactions. Sikuli is mostly used to automate flash objects and Windows-based programs. It makes use of an API that may be used and integrated into a variety of systems. Sikuli, for example, can assist in the computerization of Windows-based applications.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "automation-anywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "17. What is the difference between Automation Anywhere and Blue Prism?",
        "answer": "Automation Anywhere Blue Prism\nNot popular compared to Blue Prism. More popular compared to Automation Anywhere.\nIt offers a community edition. It offers a free edition.\nIt can be used for any medium. It can only be used for Citrix automation in the BPO field.\nIt does not require any programming language to work with Automation Anywhere. It allows users to write codes, however, it is not required.\nIt is a network computing model. It is a two-tier architecture.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "automation-anywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "18. What are the various licenses available in Automation Anywhere?",
        "answer": "In Automation Anywhere, there are two types of licenses are available:\nRun License – This license allows anyone to run the bot, but it does not allow them to make any changes.\nDeveloper License – This license allows you to create, run, and edit Bots.\nWe have some to an end to the basic Automation Anywhere Interview Questions section. Let’s move forward and read the furthermore important questions on Automation Anywhere\n\n\nIntermediate Automation Anywhere Interview Questions\nNow, we came to another section which is Intermediate level questions in this Automation Anywhere tool Interview Questions and Answers blog.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "automation-anywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "19. What are the options available in error handling?",
        "answer": "The following are the various options available for error handling are:\nErr number: to assign a mistake number that uniquely identifies the type of error.\nError Description: specifies the nature of the error.\nCapture a Snapshot: This function allows you to take a screenshot of any problem on the screen.\nRun another Task: When the current task encounters an error, this functionality is utilized to conduct any other tasks.\nLog Data Into File: This option saves the error data to a file.\nSend Email: When a mistake occurs, this functionality is utilized to send an email.\nVariable Assignment: This feature is used to define a value to be assigned and to assign tasks depending on that action\nKnow more about RPA with the RPA tutorial blog by Intellipaat.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "automation-anywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "20. How do you use Automation Anywhere system variables to create timestamps for your files?",
        "answer": "To create timestamps, use the following system variables. Additionally, you can mix the aforementioned variables to create a unique timestamp. Between each variable, you may also insert text characters.\nDate\nYear\nMonth\nDay\nHour\nMinute\nSecond\nYear\nMonth:\nDay\nHour",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "automation-anywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "21. How can you read PDFs through Automation Anywhere?",
        "answer": "By using the integration command we can read PDFs in Automation Anywhere. This command can be used to read single or multiple pages of a PDF document, extract values, merge two PDF documents, and many other things.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "automation-anywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "22. What do you mean by object cloning?",
        "answer": "Object Cloning is one of the Automation Anywhere tool’s unique instructions used for recognizing objects and various characteristics. Objects and their characteristics, such as object name, path, type, and value, are recognized by the object cloning command.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "automation-anywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "23. What are the factors that you would consider when you want to use Automation Anywhere?",
        "answer": "The following are some of the factors to think about when planning Automation Anywhere. They are as follows:\nBefore we begin planning, the first and most important thing we must do is choose an automation tool that will be beneficial to us.\nIt’s also critical to pay attention to the ideal framework’s design.\nThe test environment setup is one such component that must be considered on a case-by-case basis.\nVM/Citrix type of work environment\nType of Operating System Windows, Linux, and Mac OS\nIdentifying the test deliverables ahead of time is another important thing to consider while planning.\nThe project’s execution and schedule the timeline.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "automation-anywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "24. What is meant by the framework?",
        "answer": "The framework is a platform that can be used to create any suite, including an automation suite. This is made in such a way that it becomes more beneficial in terms of supplying adequate information on a variety of topics. Furthermore, it gives a platform for programmers to create programs for a certain purpose.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "automation-anywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "25. What are the various types of frameworks in Automation Anywhere?",
        "answer": "The following are the types of frameworks in Automation Anywhere:\nData-driven framework\nHybrid automation framework\nKeyword-driven framework\nModular automation framework",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "automation-anywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "26. What is the control room in Automation Anywhere?",
        "answer": "The control room is one of the most significant components of the Automation Anywhere architecture that serves as a web-based platform for automating processes such as execution and scheduling software bots and also managing users and clients from anywhere.\nSource control, automation deployment, a dashboard, and user administration are among the centralized features.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "automation-anywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "27. What is a Bot Creator?",
        "answer": "Bot Creators, as the name implies, are in charge of creating automation bots. These are the desktop-based programs and technologies that assist construct software bots and validate against a Live Control Room. It also allows several developers to design, upload, and download individual bots before combining them to run at the same time. The AA bot creator file extension is.ATMX",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "automation-anywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "28. What is Bot Runner?",
        "answer": "The type of machine used to run Bots is Bot Runners. Bot Runner makes it possible to operate several Bots at the same time. An Operate license is required to run any of the Bots. If there is a failure in the middle of the process, the bots are returned to the control room.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "automation-anywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "29. What is an Automation Anywhere Bot store?",
        "answer": "The Bot Store in Automation Anywhere allows developers to buy ready-to-use software bots and a digital workforce. Because the bots are pre-built, they may be deployed without any additional development. Individuals who need to automate monotonous work can benefit from bots.\nFurthermore, digital workers are the ones that can assist in the automation of company processes. As a result, Bot Store is extremely beneficial in terms of reducing development time and expenses.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "automation-anywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "30. What is Trigger and what is the use of Trigger in Automation Anywhere?",
        "answer": "The Trigger allows you to have a task run automatically in response to a certain occurrence on your computer. When a new window appears, for example, if a specific file is created, a trigger can be used. Triggers are used in Automation Anywhere to start the manager, add, delete, and edit triggers, as well as enable and disable triggers.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "automation-anywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "31. What do you know about Bot insight?",
        "answer": "Bot Insight is an embedded analytics platform that displays statistics and graphs to analyze the performance of each bot in the system. The tool simply shows the graph of each bot as well as some other key information, such as what and how the bots are working.\nThe platform creates a dashboard that summarises all analytical data. Which also assists firms in strategic planning and achieving their goals.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "automation-anywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "32. What is the difference between a set text and an append text?",
        "answer": "Set text will insert the most recent data while removing previous data, whereas add text would merely enter data without removing previous data.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "automation-anywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "33. What is the App Integration command?",
        "answer": "App Integration allows you to work with a variety of program applications such as DOS, browsers, Java applets, UNIX shells, and more",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "automation-anywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "34. What types of scripts can Automation Anywhere run?",
        "answer": "VBScript and Jscript are the two types of scripts that can be run in Automation Anywhere.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "automation-anywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "35. What is PGP? And the use of PGP?",
        "answer": "PGP (Pretty Good Privacy) is an encryption technique that may be used to send encrypted emails as well as encrypt sensitive files. By assigning the PASSPHRASE, it is utilized to ENCRYPT and DECRYPT the file.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "automation-anywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "36. In the AA assignment, how will you link or read two or more separate excel files?",
        "answer": "In AA, we can open several files/excel files at once. We need to distinguish them by giving them different/unique session names.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "automation-anywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "37. What exactly does Workflow Designer mean?",
        "answer": "When creating a process flow diagram in a graphical environment, the workflow designer comes in handy. It can be utilized in the application to create automatic tasks. The developer can use the BOTS/Tasks to execute in a flow based on a condition using the Workflow Designer.\nCheck out the Selenium Interview Questions blog by Intellipaat to crack your interview.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "automation-anywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "38. How can we extract tables from PDFs in Automation Anywhere?",
        "answer": "Manage Windows controls can be used to extract a table from a PDF document.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "automation-anywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "39. What do you know about auto-login in Automation Anywhere?",
        "answer": "Auto-Login unlocks the computer, performs the automated operations, and then restores the system to its previous state.\nThis is all about the Intermediate level AA Interview Questions. Go ahead and read some Automation Anywhere scenario-based questions.\n\nAdvanced Automation Anywhere Technical Interview Questions\nIn this section, we are going to discuss some advanced-level Automation Anywhere Interview Questions that will help you crack your technical round.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "automation-anywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "40. How do we use OCR for image recognition?",
        "answer": "Optical character recognition (OCR) is a feature that allows you to read/recognize items such as characters or images. The window for capturing, Area of Capture, Path-based picture capture, and URL-based image capture are some of the OCR options.\nThe following is the procedure for using an OCR command for image recognition:\nThe following is the procedure for using an OCR command for image recognition:\nSpecify a picture that can also be a window.\nChoose an OCR engine (TESSERACT is the default) and a threshold quantity for determining OCR accuracy.\nThe extracted text value should then be assigned to a variable.\nIt does character recognition using third-party OCR engines.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "automation-anywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "41. How can we use Automation Anywhere to read CSV files?",
        "answer": "We can read CSV files in Automation Anywhere with the two easy steps which are:\nFirst, use the command OPEN PROGRAM/FILE command to open a CSV or a text file by specifying its location.\nThen, you can use the READ CSV/TEXT FILE command to read a CSV or a text file.\nWith delimiters such as a comma, semicolon, or pipe symbol, CSV files can be separated and read.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "automation-anywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "42. Why are string operation commands used in Automation Anywhere?",
        "answer": "In Automation Anywhere, string operation commands are used to conduct a variety of tasks, such as Find, Join, Split, Trim, Reverse, Compare, Length, Before/After, Lower Case, Sub-String, and Replace.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "automation-anywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "43. What is Automation Anywhere credential vault?",
        "answer": "The Credential Manager is a centralized location for securely creating and storing sensitive information in the form of Credentials, which is used in automated operations. The Automation Anywhere credential vault allows you to save your password securely and utilize it in BOTS at runtime. These variables are easily accessible using F2 or as a password field variable.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "automation-anywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "44. What is the best way to get access to the API interaction?",
        "answer": "In Automation Anywhere, the commands REST WEB SERVICES and SOAP WEB SERVICES are used to get access to the API interaction.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "automation-anywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "45. How do I configure Automation Anywhere's email settings and SMTP server?",
        "answer": "Go to the Client Room and then to Tools to configure the email and SMTP server in Automation Anywhere. You’ll find an option for email notifications under the tools. Fill in all of the necessary information, such as the host, port number, User ID, and Password.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "automation-anywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "46. Explain steps involved in recording tasks in Automation Anywhere?",
        "answer": "We may use Automation Anywhere to record a task by following the steps below:\nChoose the SMART task recorder from the list of choices.\nSelect a RECORD button.\nUse mouse clicks and keyboard strokes to do the activities that will be recorded.\nAfter you’ve completed all of the actions and activities, click the ‘STOP’ button.\nTo save the recorded activities to a task, click the ‘SAVE’ button.\nWe can simply click the ‘RUN’ button to playback the recorded actions.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "automation-anywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "47. What do you mean by the terms least, moderately, and most friendly formats in Automation Anywhere.",
        "answer": "The file formats are categorized into least, moderately, and most friendly categories based on their complexity and readability:\nThe least friendly forms are handwritten documents, scanned papers, and PowerPoint presentations.\nWord files and typed PDFs (but not handwritten or scanned PDFs) are considered moderately friendly formats.\nExcel files, CSV files, and text files are considered the most friendly formats.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "automation-anywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "48. Can we acquire 100% automation with Automation Anywhere?",
        "answer": "Yes, we can have 100% automation with Automation Anywhere. However, it could be a difficult process. Automation depends on the company’s needs, priorities and procedures. If a human decision-making capability is necessary, the procedure will not be automated. Structured and ruled-based processes are completely automatable.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "automation-anywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "49. What are the steps you would take If you couldn’t log in to the client machine from Automation Anywhere?",
        "answer": "To resolve this issue, the following measures could be taken:\nFrom Control Room -> User Management, delete the user in question.\nCreate a new user profile using the same information as before.\nTo the newly established user profile, add a Developer license.\nRestart the user’s computer, shutting down any Automation Anywhere processes that may have been operating in the background.\nOpen the Automation Anywhere client and log in.\nIf still, the problem remains unsolved, Automation Anywhere must be installed again.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "automation-anywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "1) What is Automation Anywhere?",
        "answer": "Automation Anywhere is one of the most popular RPA tools that provides powerful features to automate complex business tasks. It is a web-based management system used to automate such processes that are repetitive, rule-based, and manually performed by humans. It offers end to end automation strategy for organizations.\nAutomation Anywhere provides the Control Room for managing the automated tasks. It is mainly used at the enterprise level and changes the way the enterprises operate. The primary aim of Automation Anywhere is to offer scalable, secure, and resilient services to its users.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "automation-anywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "Automation is a technique that is used to complete the tasks with minimal or no human intervention. This technique is used to make devices, systems, or processes to operate automatically.\nThe main purpose of automation is to boost efficiency and reduce errors from business processes. Moreover, it can provide results in less time and reduce/replace the human workforce.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "automation-anywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "3) What does RPA stand for?",
        "answer": "RPA stands for \"Robotic Process Automation\". It is a special kind of automation technique in which software robots perform a human's job to process repetitive, rule-based, and manual tasks. The technique helps organizations to automate their digital processes across various applications and systems without changing the existing systems or IT infrastructure.\nRobotic: Set of codes that help to mimic human actions is known as Robots (or bots).\nProcess: The process can be defined as the sequence of steps that creates a meaningful activity.\nAutomation: The process performed by software bots without human intervention.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "automation-anywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "Some of the main differences between Automation and RPA are tabulated below:\nParameters Automation Robotic Process Automation\nUsed for QA, Production, Performance, UAT environments. Managing production environments.\nEliminates Execution time. Manual workforce.\nCoding Requirements Required for generating test scripts. Usually not required because it is wizard-driven.\nAutomates Repetitive test cases, for example- a product. Repetitive business processes, e.g., products and businesses, etc.\nSupports Limited working environments. Wide range of supported environments.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "automation-anywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "5) What is mean by software bots?",
        "answer": "In Automation Anywhere tool, software robots (also referred to as bots) are used to automate the tasks. These software bots are nothing but a set of commands that process specified tasks in an automated way.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "automation-anywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "6) What types of bots are present in Automation Anywhere?",
        "answer": "Automation Anywhere has mainly three types of bots:\nIQ Bots: IQ Bot is an advanced tool that includes the capability of thinking like a human. IQ bots are also referred to as Cognitive bots. These bots are developed to learn on their own and perform the tasks according to encountered patterns.\nIQ bots use highly advanced cognitive technology and smart artificial technologies that enable users to experience the power of automation. These bots include features like self-learning, decision making, and subject matter expertise, etc. These bots can extract data from semi-structured and unstructured data.\nTask Bots: These are referred to as the core of automation. Task bots are helpful in automating rule-based, repetitive processes that typically rely on structured data and are easy to automate. These bots are used in the fields such as document administration, claims management, HR department, IT, etc. Tasks bots can be used to operate multi-step processes at a faster rate and with no errors.\nMeta Bots: Meta bots are generally referred to as the automation building blocks that facilitate scalability with next-generation integration. These bots are mainly used for complex, scalable processes.\nThe Meta bots can integrate DLLs (Dynamic Link Libraries) that are helpful for back end automation. Also, these bots include GUI components that are helpful for front end automation. Meta bots add simplicity for multi-level integration and enhance the automation process along with the Task bots.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "automation-anywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "7) What is BOT insights?",
        "answer": "Bot Insights is an embedded analytics platform in 'Automation Anywhere' that helps measure each bot's performance in a system. The tool simply displays each bot's graph and some other important details, such as what and how the bots are doing. The platform automatically generates a dashboard summarizing all analytical information, which helps organizations in strategic planning and achieve the project's requirements.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "automation-anywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "Some of the unique features of Automation Anywhere are listed below:\nADVERTISEMENT\nIt provides script-less automation (No programming required).\nIt can easily automate complex, complicated, and redundant tasks.\nIt uses SMART Automation Technology and offers intelligent automation for IT and business tasks.\nIt provides different types of recorders for various automation tasks, such as recording mouse clicks or keyboard strokes.\nIt has an auto-login feature with a powerful task scheduling option. It can be used to schedule tasks for automation, even when the computer is locked.\nIt can distribute tasks to different systems.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "automation-anywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "There is mainly three core components of Automation Anywhere Architecture, such as:\nControl Room\nBot Creator\nBot Runner\nAnywhere automation consists of a distributed architecture. The architecture is basically segregated into two components, Bot Creators and Bot Runner. Both of these components are attached to the Control Room, offering a centralized management system.\nThe following diagram represents a structural view of Automation Anywhere Architecture:",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "automation-anywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "10) What is mean by Control Room in Automation Anywhere?",
        "answer": "Control Room is one of the most important components of the Automation Anywhere architecture. It is a web-based platform used to manage and control software bots developed using the Bot Creators. In simple words, it acts as a web-based server that controls the bots in Automation Anywhere. Because Automation Anywhere follows centralized management, the Control Room offers various features such as user management, source control, license management, automation deployment, and a dashboard.\nUser Management - used to manage user access across different features and systems.\nSource Control - used to share code for the bots across different systems.\nLicense Management - used to manage purchased licenses of Automation Anywhere.\nAutomation Deployment - used for the deployment of bots in an automated way.\nDashboard - used to provide full insights of Automation Anywhere.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "automation-anywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "11) What is the role of Bot Creator and Bot Runner?",
        "answer": "Bot Creator - As its name states, Bot Creators are responsible for the creation of automation bots. These are the desktop-based applications and tools that validate against an active Control Room and help create software bots. It also enables multiple developers to create, upload, download individual bots, and merge them to execute all at once together.\nBot Runner - Bot Runner is usually referred to as the machine used to execute the created bots. One can easily execute multiple bots in parallel. However, Run License is required to execute the bots. Bot Runners are run-time clients that are usually installed on windows based systems. They can also report the execution status (log/pass/fail) back to the control room.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "automation-anywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "12) What is meant by the Bot store in Automation Anywhere?",
        "answer": "Automation Anywhere includes a Bot Store that allows developers to purchase ready to use software bots and digital workers. These bots can be deployed directly without any other development as the bots are pre-built. The bots are usually helpful for individuals to automate repetitive tasks. Besides, Digital workers are the ones who can help automate business tasks. Hence, Bot Store is very useful to save the development time as well as the development costs.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "automation-anywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "13) Is it possible to use Automation Anywhere for testing the Agile method?",
        "answer": "Yes, it is possible to use Automation Anywhere for testing the Agile method the same as that of continuous integration. But, when we have complex documentation or no need to change the agile testing requirements, we cannot use Automation Anywhere.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "automation-anywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "14) What are the main benefits of using Automation Anywhere?",
        "answer": "The following are the main benefits of using Automation Anywhere:\nNavigates Different Digital Landscapes: Automation Anywhere is capable of making adjustments according to the movements of the icons, buttons, and other user-created actions.\nBuild for Complexity: It can easily automate complex and complicated business processes and tasks that would require advanced coding skills.\nMade for Enterprises: It is deployed throughout the entire enterprise. Therefore, it enables human beings to focus on such processes that require human intelligence.\nEasy Programming: It supports automation through the front end, which does not actually require complex programming or coding skills. Even a person with no programming skills can work on this tool.\nEasy Integration: The tool is platform-independent and can be easily integrated with multiple systems.\nQuick Deployment: Because it offers drag and drops features to develop software bots, the development and deployment are quick.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "automation-anywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "15) What are the different types of recorders in Automation Anywhere?",
        "answer": "Automation Anywhere has three types of recorders, such as:\nScreen Recorder: The Screen Recorder is the most feasible method that helps in automating the task most efficiently. It can be used to record user actions like mouse clicks and movements, keyboard operations, etc.\nSmart Recorder: The Smart Recorder is used to record objects such as drop-down menus, checkboxes, list boxes, and radio buttons, and more in desktop applications. It is also known as 'Object Recorder'.\nWeb Recorder: The Web Recorder is primarily used for extracting the data from the web. It can accurately record user-actions on web-based tasks and further automate them without any coding skills requirements.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "automation-anywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "16) Why is Automation Anywhere a better approach than manual testing?",
        "answer": "There are several reasons why Automation Anywhere is a better approach than manual testing, such as:\nManual testing needs lots of additional resources.\nManual Testing consumes a lot of time.\nManual Testing is error-prone, and thus it reduces accuracy.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "automation-anywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "17) How many types of licenses are there in Automation Anywhere?",
        "answer": "There are two types of licenses in Automation Anywhere, such as:\nDev Licence: This license allows access to create, edit and run a bot.\nRun License: This license allows us only to run a bot. We cannot create or edit a bot.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "automation-anywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "18) What are the basic system requirements for Automation Anywhere?",
        "answer": "The following are the system requirements for Automation Anywhere:\nOperating System: Windows Server 2012, 2008 R2, 2003, or Windows XP, 7, and above.\nProcessor: 3 GHz or higher is recommended.\nRAM: At least 4GB.\nHard Disk Space: 200 MB or above for the installation.\nResolution: 1024X768 or higher.\nBrowser: Internet Explorer v10 or above, Chrome v49 or above, etc.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "automation-anywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "19) What is meant by the framework?",
        "answer": "The framework is defined as the platform for building any suite, such as the automation suite. It allows developers to create software products for special purposes. The frameworks are designed to make it easier for the product to incorporate features and other information on many aspects.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "automation-anywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "20) What are the different types of frameworks in Automation Anywhere?",
        "answer": "There are four different types of frameworks that are used in Automation Anywhere:\nModular Automation Framework\nKeyword-driven Framework\nHybrid Automation Framework\nData-driven Framework",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "automation-anywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "21) What are the main features of Automation Anywhere Client?",
        "answer": "The main features of Automation Anywhere Client are as follow:\nLogging: Automation Anywhere provides an option to create a log file containing information about bots. We can use the 'Log to File' command for creating a new log file.\nTask Scheduling: We can use the 'Scheduler' or 'Schedule Manager' to execute the automated tasks at specific times.\nProperties Setup: After we have created a task, we can view or change its properties using the 'General tab' option.\nFilters: We can use the 'Filters bar' to view only specific properties of any task. It is useful for creating long tasks or processes.\nHotkeys: One of the main features of automating tasks using 'Automation Anywhere' is executing tasks by pressing a keyboard button or a combination of keyboard buttons. Such keys are called hotkeys.\nTasks Debugging: With 'Automation Anywhere', we can debug our tasks before they are deployed in the main environment. It is useful for complex and lengthy automation tasks.\nTriggers: 'Automation Anywhere' provides the facility to execute built-in tasks in response to an event on the system. For example, we can use the trigger option to open any program automatically as soon as the Windows OS opens.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "automation-anywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "22) How will you differentiate a Wait command and a Delay command?",
        "answer": "The most important difference between a wait command and a delay command depends on the parameter for which we want to use the command. The Wait command is used when we want to wait for the window to open/close, or let the screen or its components change by themselves. Besides, the Delay command is used when working on loops and want to improve the performance of actions in tasks.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "automation-anywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "23) What commands are used to deal with Errors Handling in Automation Anywhere?",
        "answer": "There are mainly following two commands that are used to deal with Errors Handling in Automation Anywhere:\nBegin Error Handling\nEnd Error Handling\nThese commands also debug the errors. Apart from this, the tool also includes the following actions to handle errors:\nTake Screenshot: This option allows us to take a screenshot of the screen displaying errors.\nRun Task: This option allows us to run other tasks when the current task is giving errors.\nLog Data into File: This feature helps us log (save) the error information into a file.\nSend Email: This option allows us to send an email of the error, including all the information.\nVariable Assignment: This option is used to specify a value to be assigned and set tasks depending on the action.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "automation-anywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "Object Cloning is one of the special commands of Automation Anywhere tool that is used to recognize objects and their properties such as object name, type, path, and value.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "automation-anywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "25) Is it possible to achieve 100% automation with Automation Anywhere?",
        "answer": "Yes, it is possible to achieve 100% automation with Automation Anywhere. However, it depends on any organization's needs and priorities, whether they want it or not.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "automation-anywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "26) What is the difference between Automation Anywhere, Blue Prism, and UiPath?",
        "answer": "The main differences between Automation Anywhere, Blue Prism, and UiPath are tabulated below:\nAutomation Anywhere Blue Prism UiPath\nOffers a community edition Offers a free edition Offers a free edition/community edition\nNot as popular as Blue Prism and UiPath Popular than Automation Anywhere Most popular RPA tool\nUsed across all mediums Mostly used for Citrix automation in BPO field Used for Desktop, Web and Citrix automation\nNo coding or programming required as it offers drag-drops feature Allows users to write codes; however, it is not compulsory. No need for coding or programming skills",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "automation-anywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "27) What are the main applications of using automation anywhere in different industries?",
        "answer": "The main applications of Automation Anywhere in different industries are tabulated below:\nIndustries Using Automation Anywhere Application of Automation Anywhere\nFinance/ Accounting/ Banking Invoice processing, reporting, auditing, data entry, data validations, data migration between banking application, form filling, etc.\nHR Department Automating tasks in PeopleSoft, Email notifications and populating, etc.\nOperations/IT Creating accounts, system integration, software and hardware setup, and testing, batch processing, etc.\nSales Invoice creation, printing, managing customer data in CRM, etc.\nMarketing Creating lead generation reports, monitoring social sentiments, etc.\nManufacturing Inventory management, data monitoring, automating logistics data, price comparison of products, and ERP automation, etc.\nGovernment Automate regular reports, integrate legacy systems with the latest systems, verify, populate subcontractor form, etc.\nHealthcare Patient data management, medical bill generation, insurance and claim processing, eligibility, and status check, reporting for doctors, etc.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "automation-anywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "28) What is the process of creating a timestamp for the file using Automation Anywhere?",
        "answer": "Automation Anywhere provides pre-defined system variables that we can use to automate tasks on any computer. We can check the available variables from the 'Variable Manager'. The following is the list of some such system variables that can create a timestamp:\nYear\nMonth\nDay\nHour\nMinute\nSecond\nDate\nBy using these variables in the combination, we can create a timestamp of our choice.\nFor example, we can use the following command to append Year, Month, and Day at the end of any word (here we are using the word 'Demo'):\nDemo $Year$$Month$$Day$.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "automation-anywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "29) What is the role of the hotkey in Automation Anywhere?",
        "answer": "A hotkey is a shortcut key that can be used to easily execute tasks in the Automation Anywhere Enterprises edition. It makes the execution of tasks simpler and quicker.\nTo assign a hotkey to a task, we can use the following steps:\nSelect a task\nClick on the properties\nClick on the hotkey\nChoose a key or a combination of keys from the keyboard\nThat is how we can configure hotkeys and launch any specific task just by pressing a single key.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "automation-anywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "Depending on the complexity and readability, the file formats are classified into least, moderately, and most friendly categories:\nLeast Friendly: Handwritten documents, scanned documents, PPT are defined as the least-friendly formats.\nModerately Friendly: Word files and typed PDFs (doesn't include handwritten and scanned PDFs) are defined as the moderately-friendly formats.\nMost Friendly: Excel files, CSV, and text files are defined as the most-friendly formats.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "automation-anywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "31) What are the steps to record tasks in Automation Anywhere?",
        "answer": "To record a task in Automation Anywhere, we can follow the steps given below:\nSelect the SMART task recorder from the options.\nClick on a 'RECORD' button.\nPerform the activities using mouse clicks and keyboard strokes that are to be recorded.\nClick on the 'STOP' button after the completion of the actions and activities.\nClick on the 'SAVE' button to save the recorded activities to a task.\nAfter following all the steps, a new task is created with the recorded actions and activities performed on the computer. We can simply playback the recorded actions by selecting the task and then clicking on the 'RUN' button.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "automation-anywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "32) Can Automation Anywhere work when a computer is locked?",
        "answer": "Yes, Automation Anywhere can work even when a computer is locked. Because of its secure Auto Login feature, it can run a task at a scheduled time. We can schedule a task and enable the Auto Login feature to set up an entire process. When the Auto Login feature is applied to a task, Automation Anywhere will automatically unlock the system, run scheduled tasks, and lock it back.\nBesides, Automation Anywhere also offers an option to run tasks in the stealth mode. It means that the execution of tasks will be processed as scheduled but in the hidden mode. To use stealth mode, we are required to enable this option using the following steps:\nSelect a task.\nClick on the Properties.\nClick on the Security.\nClick on the checkbox displaying an option; Run this task in stealth mode.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "automation-anywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "33) Is it possible to use a password with Automation Anywhere tasks?",
        "answer": "One of the wonderful features of Automation Anywhere is to use a password with the tasks. Using this feature, we can easily password-protect our task by clicking on the 'Password Protection' checkbox and then specifying a password before saving it. Additionally, we can also create a password on our saved tasks by going into the Security tab from the main screen of Automation Anywhere.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "automation-anywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "34) What is meant by Workflow Designer?",
        "answer": "Workflow Designer is an inbuilt feature of Automation Anywhere that allows us to easily create a graphical representation of business processes. It is helpful when we require to create or automate longer tasks. Because building a process-flow structure diagram with a graphical interface is a lot easier than using complex or complicated programming. According to the specified condition, BOTS/Tasks are executed in a sequencing flow of manner.\nRunning a workflow is almost similar to running any individual task. Here are the steps:\nOpen MyWorkflow from the main screen.\nClick on the 'RUN' button given in a row of a particular workflow.\nAdditionally, we can run any workflow directly from Workflow Designer using the 'RUN' button during the workflow creation. The benefit of running a workflow using the Workflow Designer is that it highlights the part of the workflow being executed. Also, it highlights the entire path of execution after the workflow has completed running.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "automation-anywhere"
    },
    {
        "question": "35) What is the role of triggers in Automation Anywhere?",
        "answer": "In Automation Anywhere, the trigger feature enables us to automatically launch any task in response to a particular event on our computer.\nFor example, we can trigger a file containing a daily routine list to be launched automatically as soon as the system starts.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "automation-anywhere"
    }
]